okay hello it's September 16th
we're in
cohort one of the active textbook group
it's uh meeting 15.
or I guess uh yes no 16.
on um let me just update the title
meaning 16 we're in our second
discussion on chapter six so
are there any
overall comments that people would like
to
address about chapter six
or any other questions or points to add
or just areas of chapter six that they
found to be interesting
distinction between the interceptive X
receptive uh
modalities
which have been mentioned in box 6.1
and
first I think Kristen with my Michael
Allen if I'm not mistaken uh has
published a recent paper just today uh
exactly on that topic in which they've
somehow tried to provide a computational
model for the first time for the
unification of the intercepted the next
receptive modalities so since this
chapter is also that
the modeling of those agents I think
this paper from
in the body's eye the computational
anatomy of interceptive inference might
be relevant for anyone who wants to
model these modalities
for the aid of active inference
framework
thank you very nice thanks for sharing
it um
let's look at box six one
as people see it what distinguishes
exteroceptive proprioceptive and
interoceptive modalities
for example why are proprioceptive and
interceptive separated
and because
uh I couldn't hear you I don't know if
it's on my side or oh connection was
unstable from your side sorry
let me try something I'll be gone for a
second
am I back
okay so yeah what uh yeah Brock I do
need the starlink
why are proprioception and terraception
separated
and why are these three categories
modeled as different why have they been
framed as different
biological and neurological mechanisms
and neural mechanisms that
somehow can
control those
different kind of perceptions because uh
for the extraceptive perception
the organism would necessarily meet
would necessarily need a kind of
sensory
I mean the sensation it gets from the
environment is just
um on the level of its uh
of the imminent stimuli that it gets
from the external environment but for
the interceptive uh modality uh the
sensation is just the internal uh
Sensations and so on and for the
proprioceptive it's related to motor
control uh feedback loop so I guess
because of their different
mechanisms it
might be helpful to talk in different
terms about each of them but I'm not
totally sure about that
I agree I think one aspect even in a
pre-blanket or non-blanket modality is
like they're about external things
versus about internal things and then
between proprioception and interception
you're absolutely right that
they have different neural mechanisms
and physiological mechanisms
um
with some blurry space perhaps for
example like interception about blood
pressure
is somewhere in between like a muscular
reflex and uh in organ reflex but the
tissues being addressed are different
let's look at this paper
again we'll we'll return to the book but
we're going to be thinking today and
then especially going forward with like
how do you
identify
the
um
let's go to this question which we we
just just to look at it
which system are we modeling
what is the appropriate form for the
generative model
how do we set up a generative model
how do we set up a generative process
so let's see if we can determine some of
those aspects
in this paper
#figure four three
it is the very same
okay this is just a general pointing to
a partially observable Markov decision
process
with a slight
um plus computational biology graphical
veneer to match the color scheme
probably not but but it kind of looks
like it
here
is where we see this schematic
of the form of the generative model
variables are used
to reflect that those variables can be
fit from empirical data or just a priori
set and simulate it but this is the form
of the model
these are the shapes of the matrices and
tensors
that
go from
that are going to address
what their model is about
um does anybody want to like
describe what they see in this
what do you think they were trying to
explain
and what do you think they were trying
to model what is their system of
Interest based upon what you see here
uh actually one interesting term that
came up with
I mean used in this paper is uh
cardiac active inference the term that
they've been they've used in this paper
to describe uh the kind of
interrelationship between the heart
rhythm and uh the I mean the
interception so this generative model uh
I believe is uh just about
modeling that relationship between the
heart rhythm and the interception so
uh we can see as usual the B matrices c
and a matrices that we've seen before
and but in this case uh they've applied
uh to the
uh variation in the heart rhythm and how
it relates to the interception and so
yes
so
again using the variables that we know
from figure four three in the book and
their figure one here
the hidden states that are not directly
observed
are on the interceptive side relating to
the state of the heart
on the exteriorceptive side whether
there is a flower or a spider
the outcomes that are observed are the
visual exteroception of a flower or a
spider
and the heart rate
probably a low and a high heart rate
the piece that links these two
is the sensory attenuation
between the high heart rate states
and the mapping of exteroception
in the B Matrix you can just see that
even the the allocation of the symbols
is different
like when you're aroused
when you're in this this is like heart
open and then heart contract
so when you're in the aroused
situation B is how the hidden States
change their time
you're always going to go from here
to here
whereas in the relaxed situation
sometimes you go to the from this state
to this one
other times you're relaxed and so you
actually you dwell within that state
so here it's like pump rest pump rest
pump rest
here
it's 50 slower just it depends on the
parameters but it's 50 slower because
sometimes
you're going to go from one but it looks
like as it's here that it's actually
like or it's twice as slow
rest rest beat rest rest beat
so these are the two interceptive states
one has a preference
for having relaxed Hearts when flowers
are around
and having contracted heart when spiders
the a matrix maps on these two sensory
modalities
between
hidden States and outcome States
just like any a matrix would do in any
pumdp
and then there's also a transition
Matrix
of the generative process
so it's a very simple generative process
where either flowers or flowers
or spiders or spiders
as they would say you can use standard
routines
to simulate these techniques I hope that
that the code are available
you can plot
parameter sweeps
as you explore the beta and the alpha
yeah so here's like the beta parameter
and Alpha parameter
so you can do parameter sweeps with this
grid search or other approaches
and then do statistics on those outputs
is this quote active inference well it's
the output of a parameter sweep on an
active inference model
there's various other kinds of methods
so not to spend too too much time on the
paper but
um
does anyone have any thoughts on like
that
case
or how they see it applying to chapter
six's content
I think it speaks to a um
fulfillment cycle in active inference
research
oh
this work example helps a lot
I mean if anyone wants to uh
especially because uh describing this
kind of cardiac active inference as
a kind of
system that has a definite Mark of
blanket uh it was a really interesting
question at the first place and uh I
think they've done
uh really
um great job obviously in that regard
and thinking really creatively and out
of the box
uh about how we can describe that whole
system uh with Native
using markup blankets to describe its
internal and external environment and so
on
it also
um relates to this earlier question
so how does the figure four three
paradigm
discrete and continuous State spaces
with all the
attending complexities do you hear me
Ellie
okay yeah
okay okay how does this representation
connect to
um can you hear Daniel because yeah
it's a story for another day some of the
incredible
the truly incredible internet
I'm gonna try one thing so I think that
or Holly
I'll try something
foreign
here's what's interesting with the Wi-Fi
and then we'll continue because it's not
it's not a Wi-Fi learning group but with
the hot spot
there are a set of people who I cannot
interact with
but with Wi-Fi I am able to interact
with those people
just a note
so
we see the pomdp representation
now
what is not in this paper
here is a graphical layout
of the pomdp
okay
what is not in this paper
a figure six one
or indeed a figure one one
representation
so why is that
uh I'm not sure I've understood your
question quite clearly but
uh could you please elaborate on that a
little bit yes yes sure so when we look
at papers like vassal at all
communication is active inference social
and active active inference loops loops
loops you know Falcon at all remote
teams loops loops loops
Markov blanket interface
Loops entities things
yet in the application
what is specified is not the loopy
situation
what needs to be specified is chapter
six
not chapter one
so I find that very interesting
because so much of the focus attention
discourse
has been around abstractions around
Markov blankets
and their interpretations from various
stances and about boundaries physical
boundaries and conceptual boundaries
but it's a non-controversy
when it's written this way
and there are Markov blankets between
many of these variables
because it's a Bayesian graph that's not
fully connected so every Bayesian graph
that's not fully connected has Markov
blankets trivially
but this paper doesn't
need to describe
what is this is enough to say what's
inside and outside the organismal Markov
blanket if you want to even think about
it is like here in this line kind of not
not on the base graph
but it's between
The Spider and the flower outside
and the vision of The Spider and the
flower
but that's like
taken care of
with the a matrix of the exteroceptive
modality
which is I think why this
recipe
does not
Focus
on which thing are we modeling
but rather which system are we modeling
and yes we're going to pursue the
generative model before the generative
process even though they may have
symmetry or they may be very similar
um
but I just find it very interesting open
to hearing what people think like why
the cybernetic Loop action perception
Loop
is used
so much
in contrast with the form
of the model that's actually implemented
which is a it's a different topology in
a different discussion
I know that they're integrated and
compatible
uh just one comment on that is you see
at least to my understanding uh markup
blanket is a kind of
uh the kind of think modeling tool or a
kind of uh a way of thinking about the
basically the ontology of I mean the
Anthology in the sense of philosophy
it's philosophical use the ontology of
the system that we're about to model so
uh it's not necessarily uh the
relationships among the different
components of the markup blanket is
there's something not necessarily
physical or tangible relationships in
that system so it might be uh kind of
just informational
as as we've just
we saw in I think chapter five if I'm
not mistaken uh the information passing
among the different components and so on
so uh at least I think the reason for
not using uh the schematic model of
markup I mean the cybernetic model of a
markup blanket instead of uh using just
the schematic form uh probably it's
because of this uh kind of uh non let's
say non-physical or non-tangible
relationship among the different
components by non-tangible and
non-physical I mean something that can't
be
explained in terms of its uh ontological
existence if
I don't know if I would I could
express myself in that regard or not but
thank you ali um Brock and anyone else
um I was just going to
I don't know um I I feel like personally
I'm just kind of at my
um the affordances that I have to
um
get pragmatic and epistemic value here
without like doing some modeling of some
kind
um
yeah I don't know that's just good
thanks I mean this is the the second
discussion on chapter six
and then
this is setting us up to actually pursue
a model so we should be providing these
things yes I'm just yeah I'm just saying
it it's definitely ripe for that
I I mean yes uh Rohan
uh yeah so uh actually just to get some
clarification
you're asking why
the form of the model is as mentioned in
Japanese given in chapter six which is
chapter one
yes I mean they're they're compatible
topologies that actually are describing
an overlapping set of notes
I was just calling attention to the the
um amount of discourse and focus
on the potentially more familiar
more schematic
action perception Loop
and the way that that draws so much
attention to the organism environment
interface
whereas when it comes to the empirical
modeling
that interface never had to be specified
as like a first class
type
it just was included by the by
we just said there are spiders and
flowers out there hidden States s and
then there's observations of and and
there I there's no error
there's no errors
there would be no error in the
generative process itself the model
might have better right so
um so there would be the I mean that
comes from some measurement issue right
so so when you measure it and
you confuse say spider for flower or
flower for spider then you would get
some error and then maybe that's where I
guess you can talk about the Marco
blanket
uh with specifying or misobserving
something
so I I'm not sure
what what exactly is thinking yeah
I mean they're compatible right so
in this case there's no error but if
there was error obviously there would be
something wrong
empty
let me actually just correct this I
believe be I mean I I didn't mean to say
this is the visual error this is saying
that they're unchanging the flowers so
it's either they're either one or the
other here parametrically it's possible
to introduce visual error in the a
matrix
but I'm I'm just pointing to the the
architecture of the model
doesn't require even engaging with this
it's totally compatible
and the observations are the set States
and the actions are the active States
and so on
but
as presented
and as constructed
we if we're going to use a pomdp
architecture
we don't necessarily even need a
representation like this
yeah
Jessica
okay that's interesting
[Music]
hi yes I
for me the reason why
like it's like two part like the reason
why they they send um crap is so popular
and I think maybe it's also the reason
why it was
used and this is the Simplicity to show
the concept and the relationship
so like the new one
it it's great for I guess for the paper
that it was created but it doesn't show
the relationship as clear as the other
ones it's very simple
so I think that's why it was used maybe
like we move a lot of extra information
that the second paper illustrate like
study in it
but the Simplicity of that graph is why
like it really encapsible the concept
and it's also the reason why it's so
popular because it's so simple
so I think that's you know with a
relationship I think
I don't know how I see it
yep totally makes sense thank you
um and once we see that there is a
mapping
from the schematic cybernetic View
then we can probably fill in a lot of
the parts of the pmdp but just to look
One More Level here I mean the code I
posted the code below
so it's in Matlab
which people may or may not have access
to
oh sorry okay um Ali and then Ron
no I just wanted to point out one thing
that I forgot to mention before uh one
thing that might be helpful to keep in
mind is that actually in this generative
model there is a kind of unification or
kind of integration of interceptive and
extraceptive modalities because uh as
they pointed out in the paper uh this
agent this agent that they're modeling
uh adopt two modes of Engagement with
the world uh one of which is the relaxed
and the other one is uh the arouse
aroused mode of Engagement and because
of that there are two sorts of hidden
States related to each intercept of an
extraceptive one uh so I guess uh if
they wanted to put that kind of uh into
relationships between uh these kind of
modalities in that uh simplified
schematic model it wouldn't necessarily
clarify these kind of integration
between the the modalities so one reason
might be related to that I mean peculiar
a case of a particular situation of this
particular case here
thanks it also speaks to the step in the
model of the form of a generative model
and then I think when people get married
to
um the cybernetic scheme
you can imagine well then there's two
nodes inside of the internal States
there's two modes you can go between but
now you're like mixing and matching what
arrows mean where some of the arrows are
reflecting causal influence and some of
them are reflecting transitions between
mutually exclusive States
and so then we end up back into the
wireframe nightmare
where it's like a schematic
where some edges are tactile connections
and some are causal links and some are
mutually exclusive transfers of
information and all these other ways
that people visualize models
and this representation reminds us that
we're dealing with variables and states
and their connections Jessica
so I think that was from before okay but
yeah but I guess yes I think it's like
the visual
it has to do with what are you trying to
convey in that moment and you know how
much depth of information do you need I
think like at least say like for this
one you need extra information so that
all the model wouldn't work
well
just share like with the idea of what
the model is maybe this
um
version with the extra information might
be too complex for the other ones
there's a better purpose but it's like
what is the purpose he's trying to you
know
accomplish and what do you want to
communicate and depending on that then
models with more information and less
information are more successful
yep thank you totally agree I mean they
didn't do any of the loop at all they
just went straight to the pmdp
representation and also this isn't the
only form of an enteroceptive
extrareceptive integration model
one could brainstorm a whole host and
again that's what the recipe is for well
we could have a mutually exclusive
transfer
between these two states defined by
these two B matrices
which entails a policy variable
switching between the two
or we could have a continuous variable
called arousal and arousal is engaged in
some sort of attenuation relationship
here
so this isn't even the only form but it
shows us a form
um
okay
soon
in 20 minutes
we're going to be heading into chapter
7.
so let's preview it
so that when
we're working on this in the next week
preparing our questions starting to
think about what we want to be modeling
we'll kind of know what's going to
happen
all right chapter seven is active
inference in discrete time people can
still hear me okay I think so all right
so
here is where
we crossed the Rubicon
with modeling
this is abstract up till now
you cut out there for a second oh okay
okay I'm it's all good now
uh yeah just okay let's start from the
review thank you chapter seven we're
Crossing the Rubicon
together
and um it's been abstract up till now
first what is addressed
is perceptual processing
you'll find a lot of resonance between
this chapter 7.
and
step by step
which is model stream one
maybe it's step hyphen
yeah this paper step-by-step tutorial
is going to do a certain walk through
of adding incremental complexity into
the model in terms of model parameter
depth okay it's model stream one there's
four streams that Ryan and Chris White
did
static perception
Dynamic perception
Dynamic perception with preferences and
free energy minimization
Dynamic perception with free energy
minimization and flexible policy
selection through uncertainty modulation
we're going to do something similar in
chapter 7.
they
don't do that upper left corner of Step
by Step they go straight to Hidden
Markov models
for dynamic perception
this is analogous to a common filter or
any other number of General Bayesian
filtering schemes we have a prior d
hidden States s
and a sequence of observables through a
Time T that are mapped to Hidden States
a b describes how hidden States change
their time
so we have the temperature is a hidden
variable
and then we're getting observations from
the thermometer
that are mapped to the real temperature
by a Maybe it's a good thermometer maybe
it's biased or whatever
and then there's the temperature
changing Through Time
then there's a very um ali-centric
discussion of listening to music
this has to be one of the most glaring
errors in the textbook
it's very Warhol like though so maybe it
has a certain aesthetic to it
um but the example that's going to be
provided is like a musical listening
example
so
um the
a matrix is emitting notes
based upon the hidden state which is the
score of the music
the B Matrix is and seven they have 70
accuracy so this one-tenth distributes
through the Matrix
so it's just to use like integers here
but really this is like
0.7.1.1.1 because it has to add up to
one
but when this person when the hidden
state of the score is
in the first note they play it seventy
percent of the time and then the other
three notes they make an error ten
percent of the time each time
um seventy percent of the time the
musician hits their note
the B Matrix is how things change
through time the hidden state so this is
the transitions in the score
and here there's a 97 probability again
it's distributed throughout with this
one over a hundred just to represent it
with integers
and there's a prior with no uncertainty
or ambiguity of just it begins in the
first position
and so this we can even see like
you know I I don't want to use ABCD but
it would be like b c d a
in the musical ontology so here's b c d
a like that but then there is an error
in this one simulation run it'd be
probabilistic but they're showing for
didactic reasons a run where the third
what point in the third observation
there is an error
however it's heard as the correct value
that's a pure inference example this is
not active inference
this is just Bayesian models of
perception
this kind of sessile creature is rather
uninteresting
okay
Now we move from a hidden Markov model
Crouching Tiger Hidden Markov
into a partially observable Markov
decision process
a hidden Markov model is a partially
observable Markov model
because some parts of it are hidden some
are not but the key piece here is the
introduction of the decision
we know that we model that with policy
that influences how States change
Through Time
and that policy selection is governed by
G
figure four three
people can still hear because I see all
these like Frozen for me
okay okay all right okay thank you yeah
it's just strange stuff
um here's four three again
here
when we're talking about policy
selection
we're talking about states that haven't
happened yet observations and hidden
states that haven't happened yet
we see a restatement of equation 2.6
with expected free energy
here broken into epistemic and pragmatic
value
now to flesh out
this pomdp
we turn to a classic par and friston
example
which is the teamace
we're not going to go through every
single part of this teammate right now
but it'll be a key area for us to unpack
why do the matrices have the dimensions
that they have
where are the where are the four
locations that the mouse can be
you know here
down at the bottom to the left or to the
right
so this is not like a mouse moving in
continuous space it's like there are
four locations that can be in those are
the columns
there's five
hidden states of location
which we can see are Ike based upon
whether when it goes down to the bottom
to get a q
whether the hidden state is going to
reveal the Q or not
and then figure seven four and seven
five
you'll see differ first off one of them
is bolded this one is bolded this one's
unbolded
but here we see a one in the L column
because the black is on the L
and here we see a one in the r column
because the block is on the r
so understanding why that is
is going to be the Crux of understanding
how to construct
an epistemic informative cue
as a hidden environmental variable
in a generative model
here are the B matrices
transition probabilities
here's the preference vector
we'll talk about what C1 and C2 are
here are the priors
we'll talk about what D1 and D2 are
now there's more unpacking
of the epistemic value itself
so in the equation above there was a
restatement of equation 2.6 which
partitions the expected free energy into
the negative epistemic value and the
pragmatic value
now we're going to follow up
on the epistemic value
I of Pi the epistemic value of a policy
and break that down
into these representations
here are simulations
simulated epistemic and pragmatic
behavior of a rat foraging in a
teammates
so we'll try to model what these runs
are
I think it might be one small note about
the book that especially if they knew
that it was going to be black and white
which it seems like that was known
this is not Ultra helpful
perhaps people disagree
but another one this is what
said another Warhol
yeah this one this one you can even see
the Campbell Soup
but this I I think if someone was
familiar with reading these traces
they would still want to understand what
these different lines were
and like what the dashed one is
but if people are unfamiliar reading
these kinds of error residual traces
I don't know what is being shown here
um
figure 7.7
that was the simulation of the Rat
getting the epistemic cue and going to
the left
so instead of just taking a 50 50 shot
on where the food was
the rat
navigates this explore exploit dilemma
it engages in an epistemically oriented
action or an action driven by epistemic
value
to to reduce uncertainty get the cue
and then it secures the food
in this box 7-1
we see a discussion about
parameterization of uncertainty
and how Precision is the inverse of
variance
and this Omega
is the Precision variable here
just like Mark salms uses but others use
different ones
um
the lower this value is
the more even things are
and so this this has come up in the ice
cream example with the folk psychology
live stream
like if your C Vector is
[Music]
um
0 6 negative six
versus zero 500 negative 500 that's like
a sharper preference
distribution
so it's the quantitative values in the C
for example that's specified not just
the direction but also the intensity of
preference and then analogously
Precision can be specified in a
continuous form
here is a reference to a earlier par and
friston work on vision
that has to do with ocular motor
foraging which is heavily epistemically
driven
but then
they
um are using this example
to explore how precision
the viewer shows a version to the upper
left Square when it is specified with a
less precise
more ambiguous likelihood mapping
the lower left square is epistemically
attractive when the transition
probabilities are specified as more
uncertain
we'll try to understand these examples
learning a novelty 7.5
here we take that pomdp
and like we push it back in the
genealogy
now
we have a priors on the hidden states
which are themselves equipped with prior
beliefs
these are dear shlay conjugate priors
but they can be of other forms but
they're just shown as dirichlet here
because it's like a convenient
statistical distribution family
four variational inference which we
explored in several chapters ago
um these can be considered as hyper
priors
because they they but in the end just
variables on a graph and it's not like
they're tagged with being a hyper prior
and you can imagine priors that Nest on
them
exploring these potentially open-ended
Bayesian graph structures is why it's so
important to have structure learning
like Carl has pointed out for years and
why we want to have parameter sweeps
across cognitive model structures in
active block prints Because Why Stop why
not have another prior on this one
so we should have the notation and the
capacity to sweep that
here is a discussion on conjugate priors
a conjugate prior
means that when used to perform Bayesian
inference the posterior belief will be
the same type of distribution
so previously we talked about how like
the hidden State could be a continuous
variable and then the internal State
could be like a discrete variable you
know the temperature is continuous
outside and then inside is it hot or is
it cold is like what I'm caring about
so the families don't have to match
but when we use conjugate priors
it makes it so that
where you can design it to play nice it
does play nice
but we'll work through that
also with anybody who wants to go into
more detail on the math and because
these are just like Bayesian statistics
points
here Theta is used to just describe
parameters it's a very common notation
but not 100 pervasive to use Theta for
parameters just generally
um
here there's more unpacking of the
update rules this is probably of
secondary consideration for just
constructing a model
here we return to expected free energy
and several more representations Beyond
What was seen above and beyond what was
seen in equation 2.6
here the learning model that was
presented above the um pomdp with
another generation of genealogy
is described which is drawn from these
two papers
then structured learning is introduced
we'll see how deep this one goes but
these papers are quite
interesting and connected to Bayesian
model reduction
here a hierarchical model is presented
here's figure four three in the dashed
box
now there's a figure four three you know
yo dog I heard you liked figure four
three
then there's another hierarchical model
simulation from the above
showing belief updating again with these
Trace diagrams
and then
There's a summary
so it's a somewhat long
chapter
it contains like the music example the
rat example
[Music]
um
the maze example the eye example
so we're seeing like data points in
model space
[Music]
um
in the last three minutes does anyone
have any thoughts or questions how are
they going to tackle chapter seven
and as they start to construct their
model if they want to
I am just a
um
every direction click that I can because
it is
quite dense still and kind of
unapproachable I think for me anyways it
just is quite difficult to like get a
grasp on it from
the textbook specifically
um
at this point like the degenerative
model like what does that mean in code
and where does that correlate to this
particular function or that particular
time step or whatever
um it's you know I don't know it's just
a lot
and so I'm just trying to
from yeah I don't know from just
um
generally building up simulations which
are just things that you can you know
put together in a browser like with
simple JavaScript to like
CAD Cad and active block rents and you
know these sorts of things and
trying to
grasp at some real world situation so
maybe that that rat you know teammates
is a
really good place to focus on
um for me like a good intersection
between the book and something that
isn't like the frog jumping or is it not
jumping is
you know so contrived it's really
difficult to think about modeling that
and in a way that would help explain
what's going it's like yes I knew the
Frog was jumping or not jumping so that
doesn't really help right
um whereas
the rat maybe coming up with some left
or right hidden State based on the queue
that's partially it's there's
some explanatory power there that maybe
realized I think so um
I'm just yeah I don't know it's
I'm trying to bridge jump over the Grand
Canyon of the philosophical conceptual
okay got it but the math there's a okay
but there's a gap there for me so I'm
trying to pull them together and it's
uh yeah I have a question related to
calibration of those priors and among
other things
uh is that ever explained as to how to
go about doing that for
any of these models
yes
so
um
model based data analysis
is going to describe okay so it's it's
okay it's in the future all right yeah
I'll be for that chapter seven describes
just in our last minute chapter 7
describes the discrete State models
chapter 8 describes continuous time
models chapter 9 describes using
empirical data for model driven data
analysis chapter 10 is a summary
the textbook is you know
yeah we're excited towards the Grand
Canyon but I think again we have several
months to unpack this together so I hope
that we can go quite far with this so
um please stay engaged and add your
questions and start building from both
sides play with the code examples
provided break them and then start from
the other side with a recipe on a
situation that you care about and then
they're going to meet in the middle
okay
thank you everyone
farewell
bye